Sepehr **Razmyar**

Tehran, Iran

🛘 +989215207826 | 💌 sepehrjamshid@hotmail.com | 🌴 null3rror.github.io/Portfolio/ | 🖸 Null3rror | 🛅 Sepehr-Razmyar | 😘 live:sepehrjamshid

Summary_

Unity programmer. BS in Computer Engineering in progress. Skilled in Unity & C#. Strong knowledge on design patterns, principles & best practices.

Skills

Programming C#, C++, C, Python, Bash scripting, Writing clean, reuseable & readable code

Parallel Programming Compute Shaders, CUDA, OpenMP, Intel SIMD

> Testing Unit testing, Mocking

Networking Wireshark, GNS3, Encryption, Network protocols, OpenVPN, Squid Proxy

Tools Git, Version control

Mathematics University level math, 3D mathematics **Problem Solving** Algorithms, Data structures, Bit masking

Microcontrollers Experience with embedded systems design using the Arduino programming environment

Work Experience

Pars Cog, University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Jul. 2021 - PRESENT UNITY GAME DEVELOPER

· Currently performing as Software Architect & Unity Developer developing & architecting game components

Developed 2D & 3D Corsi Block for visual/auditory memory improvement

Amytis Games Tehran, Iran

UNITY GAME DEVELOPER INTERN Jul. 2019 - Sep. 2019

• Programmed an configurable 2D enemy AI with animations

- Improved their path system from waypoint based to Bezier spline by implementing an editor tool which you can edit the spline in scene view
- Programmed a matchmaking system using Photon Networking
- Programmed camera control for a mobile game

Projects

Haft Peykar's Turquoise Dome

Tehran, Iran

Jul. 2021

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

· Haft Peykar is a romantic epic by Persian poet Nizami Ganjavi written in 1197, in this project we can see Turquoise dome

• Responsible for shaders, particles, level design & scripts

S.P.H.E.R.E Tehran, Iran

Jun. 2021

· Based on Trials Evolution's mini game, this game was developed to represent our Xbox Remote Controller

A Man Looking for His Organs - Global Game Jam 2020 🗹

Tehran, Iran

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

Feb. 2020

• 2D platformer game developed in 48 hours, with theme of "Repair"

• The player has to fight enemies, gather his organs & shoot his way out

Prince of Persia's rewind mechanic 🗹 | 🛗

Tehran, Iran

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

Jul. 2019

• A 3rd person game which you can rewind time like Prince of Persia

Pacman using A* algorithm 🗹 | 🛗

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

Jul. 2019

· Pacman game were each ghost has different strategy

• Ghosts use A* algorithm to track Pacman

Tank Trouble using PyGame im

SOLO PROGRAMMER & ARTIST

Tehran, Iran

Jan. 2018

- Tank Trouble clone developed using PyGame
- Supports multiplayer, Xbox & PS4 controllers
- Implement horde (survival) mode with waypoint based Als
- Implement shotgun, big ball & shield power up

Nerf Gun as a VR Gun Contoller

Tehran, Iran Jul. 2021

SOLO PROGRAMMER

- Turned a Nerf gun to a gun controller for PC, Xbox, PS4 games which acts as a mouse & keyboard using Arduino
- Pull the trigger in real life, it'll shoot in game
- Reload in real life, it'll reload in game
- Use the buttons & thumb stick to walk, jump, interact etc.
- · Works on every FPS game
- Melee in real life, it'll melee in game, check the video for more details

Ballz clone using SDL Tehran, Iran

Solo Programmer & Artist

Apr. 2018

- Ballz clone developed using C++ & SDL for Advanced Programming course
- Add explosion, bricks cracking & creating dust and magnet pulling animation for balls to unify

Legend of Bounca - CPS course project (?)

Tehran, Iran Apr. 2021

ANDROID PROGRAMMER

- A physic based ball which bounces based on Android device's gyroscope or gravity sensor
- Responsible for developing & architecting game components
- · Implementing physics & collision from scratch

Xbox Remote Controller 🛗 🗘

Tehran, Iran

SERVER SIDE & ANDROID PROGRAMMER

Jun. 2021

- Your Android device can act as an Xbox controller
- Support multiplayer, up to 4 players, useful for when you're short on controllers
- · Support multiple layouts for different games, e.g., gyroscope layout for driving games
- Supports Unity games & every game that supports Xbox controller

OpenVPN over Proxy 🛗 | 🗘

Tehran, Iran

Oct. 2020

- · OpenVPN which is wrapped in HTTP packet
- Without wrapping in HTTP packet, it can't bypass DPIs

Education

University of Tehran Tehran, Iran

Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2022(Expected

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Graduation)

- Studying at Electrical Computer Engineering Faculty of University of Tehran
- Overall GPA: 3.81 / 4
- Thesis project: Developing cognitive games for visual/auditory memory improvement of children & elders Supervisor: Prof. Hadi(Manouchehr) Moradi

Certifications

Core Interaction Programming part of Unity Certified Programmer Exam Preparation Specialization,

Courserd

2021 Neural Networks and Deep Learning, 🗹

Coursera

Soft Skills

Hard working

Team working

Continuous learning

Commitment | Re

Responsible

Time management

Languages.

English Professional working proficiencyPersian Native or bilingual proficiency